Guide to the Harry F. Shaw, Jr. Papers, 1963-1973 AIS.1974.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Organizations, III.
  - Ohio Valley Regional Coalition Conference program, August 15-17, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Peace and Freedom Party, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - 1968 National Convention at Ann Arbor, 1.
    - Comments on the 1968 Democratic Convention, 2.
    - Individual political campaigns in Los Angeles and Seattle, 3.
  - Pennsylvanians for a Peace and Freedom, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    Regarding nomination of Dick Gregory for President and B. Spock for V.P.
  - Peoples' Appalachian Research Collective correspondence and annotated bibliography on coal miner's unions (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Pittsburgh Area Students for Peace (Box 2, Folder 81)
    Facsimile of a newspaper ad during an end to the bombing and names of supporters.
  - Peoples' Coalition for Peace and Justice (Box 2, Folder 82)
    Program for the Spring, 1971, linking the demand for peace with the demand to aid the poor.
  - Philadelphia Student Health Organization program from a meeting, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Pittsburgh Draft Information Center, (United Oakland Ministry) correspondence, leaflets, and pamphlets regarding the draft and draft counseling, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Pittsburgh Medical Committee on Human Rights, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    Program from "Health in the Workshop," 1972 and a report on the workshop. Publication of the national MCHR "Health Hazards in the Workplace," January 1972.
  - Pittsburgh Peace and Freedom Center, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Correspondence with H. Shaw, 1968-1971; 1.
    - "Resistance Today Alternatives Tomorrow" program, April 3-5, 1970; 2.
    - Gulf Action Project leaflet, April 28, 1970; 3.
    - Pittsburgh Area Planning Session program, 4.
  - Promoting Enduring Peace, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    Form letters, 1968-1970; reprints dealing with the: arms race, Vietnam, poverty, failure of American foreign policy, chemical and biological warfare, fascism in America, etc.; statements about Vietnam by Phillip Berrigan and J. W, Fulbright; and receipt to H. Shaw for 1969 dues.
  - Radical Education Project (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Purpose, activities, and objectives of REP pamphlet, 1.
    - "G.E.: Profile of a Corporation," by J. DeMuth, 2.
    - "Marxism: An Introduction," by M. Goldfield, 3.
    - "Power in American Society," by J. Jacobs, 4.
    - "Stock Ownership and the Control of Corps," by D. Villarejo, 5.
    - "The Subversion of Collective Bargaining," by D. Bell, 6.
    - "Toward a Student Syndicalist", 7.
  - National Committee for a SANE Nuclear Policy correspondence, resolutions, and local and national election materials, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Radical Organizing Committee statements of philosophy and demands, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference program, September 6-8, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Southern Conference Educational Fund (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Correspondence with H. Shaw - Includes a letter to the people of Kentucky stating history, purpose, and program of SCEF, 1967-1971; 1.
    - Memos, 1968; 2.
    - Resolution adopted by the Board of Directors, May 12, 1970; 3.
    - Leaflets regarding civil rights/draft resistance/Walter Collins' case; SCEF Educational Center; grape boycott; Vietnam, 4.
    - Protest against investigation by the US Senate Internal Security Subcommittee, 1967-1968; 5.
    - "Appalachia: Case Study in Repression", 6.
    - Pamphlets regarding poverty in the South, 7.
  - Southern Poverty Law Center - Letter and pamphlet outlining purpose (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Students for a Democratic Society, 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1969; 1.
    - Constitution as amended in 1966 and 1967, 2.
    - Anti-Draft Resolution, December 28, 1966; 3.
    - Nation Convention report, 1969; 4.
    - Pamphlets regarding campus organizing, history, philosophy, goals of SDS, and repression of Dr. Spock, 5.
  - Students for a Democratic Society (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - "Alienation or Participation: the Sociology of Participatory Democracy," by M. Oppenheimer, 1.
    - "A Rank and File Upsurge, "Democracy is Nothing if it is not Dangerous," by C Oglesby, 2.
    - "Don't Mourn, Organize: SDS Guide to Community Organizing", 3.
    - "Getting Ready for the Firing Line," by M. James, 4.
    - "Guide to Conscientious Objection", 5.
    - "Historians and the New Deal," by B. Wiley, 6.
    - "Movement Fund Raising Guide", 7.
    - "National Vietnam Examination", 8.
    - "Notes on the Welfare State," by B. Ross, 9.
    - "An Open Letter to the New Left," by C. W. Mills, 10.
    - "Our Fight is Here: Essays on Draft Resistance", 11.
    - "The Port Huron Statement", 12.
    - "Tenant Housing Manual", 13.
    - "Student Social Action," by T. Hayden, 14.
    - "The CIA at College: Into Twilight and Rack," by T. Gitlin and B. Poss, 15.
    - "The New Radicals and 'Participatory Democracy'" by S. Lynd, 16.
    - "The Care and Feeding of Power Structure," by Minnis, 17.
    - "Trapped in a System," by C. Oglesby, 18.
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Newsletter, v. 1, no. 4.
    - Interview with Stokely Carmichael, by W. A. Price, reporter for the National Guardian
  - Student Mobilization Committee (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Correspondence - Includes inquiry for literature from H. Shaw, 1967-1969; 1.
    - Memo regarding preliminary report on August 3-10 demonstrations, August 13, 1968; 2.
    - Conference agenda, 3.
    - Legal brief on the rights of activists, 4.
    - Conference report, December 28, 1968; 5.
    - Working Committee minutes, 6.
  - Student Mobilization Committee (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Continuations Committee reports, 1.
    - Newsletter and Strike Bulletin, 1968; 2.
    - Progress reports nos. 8-10 on Oct. 21 confrontation, 3.
    - Leaflets on anti-war, draft, and student pickets, 4.
    - Mobilizer News, 1967-1968; 5.
    - Student Mobilizer, Wallposter no. 2 regarding GIs against the war and SMC support, March 14, 1969; 6.
    - The Boston Mobilizer, 7.
  - Temporary Organizing Committee for a Marxist-Leninist Youth Organization (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Organizing Convention, 1.
    - Report of preliminary meeting, 2.
    - Convention agenda, 3.
    - Speech by H. Winston, 4.
    - Correspondence to H. Shaw, November 12, 1969; 5.
    - "A Call to Found a Revolutionary Working Class Youth Organization", 6.
    - "A Plan to Win: A Draft Document on Strategy for Youth", 7.
    - "Draft Constitution", 8.
    - "Main Political Report," by J. Tyner, 9.
    - "Draft document on the World Situation", 10.
    - "Proposed Document on Working Class," by B. Fugate, 11.
    - "National DuBois Club Classes", 12.
    - "SDS Position Paper", 13.
    - Pittsburgh Youth Conference leaflet, 14.
  - The Resistance (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1970
    - Draft resistance regarding Don Ratey leaflet
    - Draft/Vietnam War demonstration at the Democratic Convention in Chicago
  - United Auto Workers - C. Wilson candidate for delegate (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - United Electrical Workers (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - "Can the Worker be Tricked into Betraying His Own Interest?" by F. J. Donner, 1.
    - "The Young Worker Challenges the Union Establishment," by J.J. Matlas, 2.
  - United Farm Workers, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1972; 1.
    - Leaflet regard to grape boycott, 2.
    - Position paper on legislation, 3.
    - "UFW Calendar - 1970", 4.
    - "Right to Work Laws A Trap for America's Minorities," by C. E. Chavez and R. Rustin (in English and Spanish), 5.
  - United Mine Workers, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Forty-sixth Constitutional Convention agenda, 1973
    - Officers' Report, "The Year of the Rank and File"
  - United Mine Workers welfare and retirement fund, 1965-1970 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Welfare and Retirement Fund application form (blank), 1.
    - Statements critical of the Fund by Rep. Ken Hecher, 2.
    - Statement defending the Fund by the Directors of the Fund, 3.
    - Annual Reports, 1965-1970; 4.
    - News release, August 10, 1965; 5.
  - United Mine Workers, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - "A Proposal to the UMWA Dept. of Manpower and Training", 1.
    - "Constitution of the International Union, UMAW", September 9, 1968; 2.
    - District 6 Newsletter, December 22, 1965; 3.
    - "National Bituminous Coal Wage Agreement of 1968", 4.
    - "The Strange Romance between John L. Lewis and Cyrus Eaton," by N. Caldell and G.S. Graham reprinted from Harper's Magazine, 5.
  - United Mine Workers District No. 5 Verbatim proceedings of the 48th Consecutive and 21st Constitutional Convention, vol. 1, April 21-24 and May 4-5, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - United Mine Workers District No. 5 Verbatim proceedings of the 48th Consecutive and 21st Constitutional Convention, vol. 2, April 21-24 and May 4-5, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - United Mine Workers District 5 lawsuit (Box 3, Folder 109)
    Lawsuit filed by Attorney Kenneth Yablonski against the International Officers to require them to disband with less than ten members.
  - United Mine Workers District 5 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Miners for Democracy campaign for district offices election, December 8, 1970; 1.
    - Platform and criticism of incumbent officers, 2.
    - Sample of official ballot, 3.
    - MFD candidate statements of their programs, 4.
    - Instruction to election observers and certificate of observation, 5.
    - Affidavits regarding Joe Rudznoski who helped destroy District 5 (1927 strike), 6.
    - List of polling places, 7.
    - News release, December 12, 1970; 8.
    - Leaflets regarding charging the present officers with permitting communists in the union, misuse of union funds, and not adequately representing the union; questioning the validity of the absentee ballot, 9.
    - Rally notices, 10.
  - United Mine Workers - Miners for Democracy, Morgantown office correspondence, receipts, and miscellaneous notes (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - United Mine Workers - District 5, Centerville Clinic - Statement regarding founding of the clinic and the facilities available (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - United Mine Workers - Miners for Democracy Nominating convention, May 27-28, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Agenda, 1.
    - Proposed convention rules, 2.
    - Credentials committee report, 3.
    - News release, 4.
    - Candidate biographies, 5.
    - "UMW Miners for Democracy Background", 6.
    - "Summary of MFD Court Cases", 7.
    - MFD survey of pensioners conducted by WVU student evaluation attached, 8.
  - United Mine Workers, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - International election, December 9, 1969; 1.
    - Platform statement of E. Wolford, candidate for UMW president, H.E. Brown, V.P candidate and L. Thornsberry, Sect Treas candidate, April 26, 1969; 2.
    - Statement of candidacy by J. A. Yablonski, May 29, 1969; 3.
    - Charges of breach of trust and corruption against incumbent officers, 4.
    - "Instructions for Official Election Observers," issue by miners for Yablonski and Brown, 5.
    - Certificate of observation issued to H. Shaw, 6.
    - Leaflets for Boyle and for Yablonski, 7.
    - Tally sheets, 8.
    - Federal election law in regard to UMW, 9.
  - United Mine Workers - Reprint from the Reader's Digest, "The Coal Black Shame of the UMW" (Box 3, Folder 115)
    Regarding the administration of Tony Boyle, the election, and the murder of Jock Yablonski.
  - "Mexico '68, the Students Speak," by United States Committee for Justice to Latin American Political Prisoners (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - University Christian Movement, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Articles of Operation of the UCM in the USA, history, goals, organizational structure, 1.
    - National Convention, 1967: resolutions regarding anti-Vietnam and urging discussion of international problems, 2.
    - National Convention, 1968: program, workshops, reports, membership roll, statement of goals, resolutions, 3.
    - 2nd Look newspaper, April-June 1968; 4.
    - "Our Story," a statement concerning UCM purpose, March 28, 1968; 5.
    - "Initial Statement of Radio Free People", May 30, 1968; 6.
    - "Student as Nigger", 7.
    - "What Makes a Campus Activist Christian?", 8.
    - Miscellaneous material from the Cleveland area UCM, 9.
  - Venceremos Brigade, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Cuba, 1970
    - Boycott Action Sheet regarding Nestle Company, Coca Cola citrus operation in Florida, and California lettuce, March 6, 1972
    - Committee for a Free Mozambique
  - Vietnam Moratorium Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1970; 1.
    - A pledge to resist the draft, 2.
    - Leaflets regarding rallies, anti-war, anti-Vietnam, the cost of the Vietnam War, 3.
    - Pamphlet regarding stopping the war, 4.
  - Vietnam Moratorium Committee memoranda, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Vietnam, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Correspondence, 1967; 1.
    - Memoranda, 1967; 2.
    - Names and addresses of the members of the national staff, 3.
    - H. Shaw's reports as field secretary, 4.
    - Miscellaneous notes, 5.
  - Vietnam (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Worklist, 1-5 and 7-8, 1.
    - Cleveland Conference program, June 18-25, 1967; 2.
    - Schedule of Trade Union Schools, Washington Meeting, Tentative Agenda, 3.
    - Evaluation of the Vietnam Summer Project by Phil Farham, 4.
    - Memoranda regarding VS participation in the Conference for the New Politics, study groups, draft, and church leafleting in Ames and Des Moines, Iowa, 5.
    - Newsletter regarding teachers against the war, 6.
    - Hazelwood (Pittsburgh area) "Project Profile: Pittsburgh Working Class Organizing", 7.
    - News release regarding the murder of G. Vissad, a VS activist in Austin, Texas, 8.
    - "What is VS" pamphlet, 9.
  - Vietnam (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - "Anti-war Labor Organizing", 1.
    - "Draft Counseling Centers", 2.
    - "VS Guide to Fund raising", 3.
    - 'VS Guide to High School Organizing", 4.
    - "VS Guide to Publicity", 5.
    - "VS Organizers' Manual", 6.
  - Vietnam - National Contact List, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - War Resistors' League, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1968; 1.
    - Memorandum, September 22, 1967; 2.
    - WRL Ballot, 3.
    - Anti-war/draft/Vietnam leaflet, 4.
    - Poor People's Campaign, 5.
    - "Information on non-payment of War Taxes", 6.
    - WRL Analysis of the Vietnam War, 7.
    - WIN literature, 8.
    - "What is the WRL", 9.
  - West Virginia Food, Nutrition and Health Conference, March 23-25, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Draft of overall conference recommendations prepared for discussion at the closing session
    - Leaflets protesting the study of not acting to alleviate hunger
  - West Virginia Service Corp, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Steering Committee correspondence to H. Shaw, 1969; 1.
    - Minutes, October 1, 1969; 2.
    - Financial statement, August 22, 1969; 3.
    - Summer project evaluation, 1969; 4.
    - Program, 1969-1970; 5.
    - Endorsement by Marshall University SDS, 6.
  - West Virginia Council of the White House Conference on Children and Youth, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Financial receipts and records, 1.
    - Booklets distributed at the 1968 Fall Conference regarding educational reform, poverty, and racism, 2.
    - Radical resolutions: anti-war, anti-draft, and asserting of student rights, 3.
    - Miscellaneous notes taken by H. Shaw, 4.
  - West Virginia Council of the White House Conference on Children and Youth correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - West Virginia Council of the White House Conference on Children and Youth, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - By-laws, 1965; 1.
    - Officers, 1967-1968; 2.
    - Statement of aims, 3.
    - Meeting notices, reports, minutes, and attendance rosters of regional meetings held throughout 1968, 4.
    - Program, October 1968; 5.
    - Suggestions and ideas from a County Youth Workshop, at Camp Muffly, 6.
    - List of people going to Washington, April 26, 1968; 7.
    - Membership application regarding H. F. Shaw, 8.
    - Membership roster and meeting agendas, 1967; 9.
  - West Virginia Council of the White House Conference on Children and Youth correspondence with Shaw, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - West Virginia Council of the White House Conference on Human Rights program and Shaw's notes, March 26, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - West Virginia Union of Students, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Draft of program, 1.
    - Draft of Constitution, 2.
    - Organizational meeting, October 4, 1970; 3.
    - Agenda for founding convention, November 21-22, 1970; 4.
    - Organizing committee, 5.
    - Newsletter, February 1971; 6.
    - Suit against WVU seeking readmission for certain students, 7.
    - Platform of the executive section of the WVU chapter, a candidate for freshman class president, 8.
    - Contact lists and resolutions, 9.
  - West Virginia Youth Awareness Conference speech by J.D. Rockefeller IV on the need to trainyouth for existing jobs (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - White House Conference on Food, Nutrition, and Health Taskforce Action Statement, December 4, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - Women Strike for Peace leaflet, pamphlets, and reprints against the Vietnam War (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - World Federation of Democratic Youth poster and leaflets (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - World Student Christian Federation (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Pamphlet outlining origin, aims and whom the WSCF it serves, 1.
    - "The Banks and Apartheid" booklet, 2.
  - Young Workers Liberation League, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Founding convention, February 7-9, 1970; 1.
    - Memorandum, August 1969; 2.
    - Call for convention and proposal, 3.
    - Sketch of YWLL history, 4.
    - Constitution, 5.
    - Biographical sketches of officers, 6.
    - Proposed rules of order, 7.
    - Resolutions and discussion topics, 8.
    - Conversation summary, 9.
    - Spring Offensive newspaper, 1971; 10.
    - Second national convention, April 14-17, 1972; 11.
    - Main political resolution, issued December 1971, 12.
    - Procedure for electing delegates, 13.
  - Young Workers Liberation League, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - "Article on the Young Coal Miner for YWLL Magazine", 1.
    - "Liberation vs. Vietnamination," by M. Zagarell, T. Monteiro & J. Schaffner, 2.
    - "YWLL," regarding its goals and principles, 3.
    - Young Worker periodical, January-February 1971; 4.
    - "Smash Racism," statement of the Central Committee, June 1971; 5.
    - "White Chauvinism," prepared by J. Edelman, 6.
    - "On Building Peace, and Anti Repression Movements, 3nd Movements against Unemployment in the Trade Unions and in the Communities," by J. Edelman, March 14, 1970; 7.
    - "Report on the Rank and File Conference," prepared by the Resident Committee, 8.
    - "Introduction to Marxism Leninism", 9.
  - Young Workers Liberation League, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Leaflets regarding Angela Davis; Attica; Organizing a legal defense committee; political support for a Black Socialist candidate for Boston School Committee; Soviet Jewry; student unrest; Vietnam; and wage freeze/black workers/labor, 1.
    - Biography of H. Winston, 2.
    - Pittsburgh Chapter YWLL: news release protesting hearings conducted by the Subversive Activities Control Board in Pittsburgh, February 1971; 3.
  - Young Workers Liberation League minutes of the Resident Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Young Workers Liberation League correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 143)
- Subject Files, IV.
  The Subject Files series contains a variety of subjects including Appalachia and the South generally; black lung and coal mining; labor and unions; race relations; poverty; and Vietnam and the draft.
  - Appalachia (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Opening of the Appalachian Movement Press, 1.
    - Education, 2.
    - Poverty, 3.
    - Folk Festivals, 4.
    - Conference program on the role of women in Appalachia, 5.
    - Rural Youth Outlook Conference, news release, 6.
    - Alternative America, program, 7.
  - Appalachia - Publications and unpublished papers (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - Appalachian labor songs, 1.
    - Poverty, 2.
    - Economy, 3.
    - Politics, 4.
    - Culture, 5.
  - Black Lung (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - T. Boyle's statement to Senate sub-Committee, 1.
    - Summary of the 1972 Black Lung Law, 2.
    - Article by Art Shields on the history of the struggle for the Black Lung Law, 3.
    - Articles on black lung by Lorin E. Kerr, MD, Department Of Occupational Health, UMW, 4.
    - UMW publications: "Black Lung Information on Black Lung", 5.
    - American Lung Association publications regarding lung diseases, 6.
    - Petition, with names, in support of the Black Lung Law, 7.
    - Miscellaneous notes, articles, handbills, notices, 8.
  - Coal Mining Industry (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Report by J Davitt McAteer on the social effects of coal mine on Appalachia, 1.
    - Statement by Sen. H. A. William on the importance of coal to the nation, 2.
    - Notes on mine safety, pollution, etc., 3.
    - Sociological studies: Knipe, E. E., and Lewis, H. M., "The Impact of Coal Mine on the Traditional Mountain Sub-Culture A Case of Peasantry Gained and Peasantry Lost", 4.
    - "Militancy Among Coal Miners in Appalachia, 1950-1970," a research proposal to the US Deptarment of Labor, by Paul J. Nyden, 5.
  - Columbia University (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - The Review of the Student Forum, vol. II, nos. 10, 17, 19, 20, 22; unnumbered note no 19 is about coal mines and coal miners, 1.
    - Leaflet in regarding an appearance by H. Shaw, 2.
  - Community Organization - Booklet by the Foundation for Community Organization, Durham, NC (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Cuba - Speech given by Fidel Castro, in regard to accomplishment in Cuba since the Revolution and future goals, July 26, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Angela Davis - Various committees to free Angela Davis, including the Pittsburgh Committee (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Draft (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Articles and brochures on the draft and conscientious objection, 1.
    - Statement by Tom Rodd to Judge Louis Rosenberg, 2.
    - Pamphlet by A. J. Muste, "Of Holy Disobedience," first published in 1952, 3.
  - Draft (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Letter from the Rockland, NY County Draft Counseling Service to draftees offering advice on how to avoid the draft, 1.
    - Sermon: "Christians must Morally Support Conscientious Objectors," by Rev. M. J. Paine, March 13, 1968; 2.
    - Instructions on legal ways to stop the draft, 3.
    - Statement by Sen. M. O. Hatfield in support of the volunteer army, 4.
    - Handbills announcing: court proceedings, urging the elimination of the draft, and rallies, 5.
  - Duke University (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Student Committee Against the War, 1.
    - Position papers on the Campus Christian Ministry at Duke, 2.
  - Election Campaigns (miscellaneous), 1968-1972 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - Citizens to draft Gavin, 1968 presidential campaign for James M Gavin, 1.
    - Dick Gregory, 1968 campaign for president, 2.
    - Bouie Haden, 1972 Congressional campaign, 3.
  - Foreign Language Presses - A list of foreign language newspapers in the US with addresses (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Hungarian Revolution - Anderson, Andy Hungary 56, Bromley, Kentucky: Solidarity, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 157)
  - Huntingdon Conference on Appalachian Problems (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - Calling to meetings with statements of purpose, 1.
    - Secretaries' report, February 14, 1969; 2.
    - Memoranda regarding the subpoena of mountain organizer to appear before the US Senate Committee on Government Operations, 3.
  - William Kunstler (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Labor (Box 4, Folder 160)